Inventory of the Consultoria Interdisciplinaria en Desarrollo public opinion data reports
Hoover Institution Archives
Consultoria Interdisciplinaria en Desarrollo public opinion data reports
1979-2004
2005C73
Consultoria Interdisciplinaria en Desarrollo, S.A.
33 manuscript boxes (13.2 linear feet)
Hoover Institution on War, Revolution, and Peace Stanford, California 94305-6010
Relates to Central American public opinion on political, social, economic and international issues.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research. Access to audiovisual materials requires at least two weeks advance notice. Audiovisual materials include sound recordings, video recordings, and motion picture film. Hoover staff will determine whether use copies of the materials requested can be made available. Some materials may not be accessible even with advance notice. Please contact the Hoover Institution Archives Audiovisual Specialist for further information.
Accruals
Increments may have been received since this finding aid was prepared. Please check Stanford University's online catalog Socrates at http://library.stanford.edu/webcat to find the full extent of the collection.
Administrative History
Public opinion polling organization based in Costa Rica and affiliated with the Gallup International Research Institutes.
Scope and Content of Collection
Relates to Central American public opinion on political, social, economic and international issues.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects
Public opinion--Central America.
Container List
- Costa Rica
  - 1979-1981 (Box 1)
  - 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 3)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 4)
  - 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - 1992-1994 (Box 6)
  - 1995-1997 (Box 7)
  - 1997-1999 (Box 8)
  - 2000-2002 (Box 9)
  - 2003-2004 (Box 10)
- Cuba, 1994 (Box 10)
- El Salvador
  - 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 11)
  - 1991-1994 (Box 12)
  - 1995-1998 (Box 13)
  - 1999-2001 (Box 14)
  - 2002-2003 (Box 15)
  - 2004 (Box 16)
- Guatemala
  - 1990, 1992 (Box 16)
  - 1993-1997 (Box 17)
  - 1998-2001 (Box 18)
  - 2002-2004 (Box 19)
- Honduras
  - 1986 (Box 19)
  - 1987-1990 (Box 20)
  - 1991, 1993-1995 (Box 21)
  - 1996-1999 (Box 22)
  - 2000-2002 (Box 23)
  - 2003-2004 (Box 24)
- Nicaragua
  - 1989-1991 (Box 24)
  - 1992-1995 (Box 25)
  - 1996-1998 (Box 26)
  - 1999-2001 (Box 27)
  - 2002-2004 (Box 28)
- Panama
  - 1981-1983 (Box 29)
  - 1994-1997 (Box 30)
  - 1998-2000 (Box 31)
  - 2001-2003 (Box 32)
  - 2004 (Box 33)